Okay. So, now we'll do the same thing as we did before,
和之前一样
painting our weights in the neural network to better classify our points.
我们在神经网络图中标记权重 以便更好地分类点
But we're going to do it formally,
但是这一次 我们将使用严谨的表达式
so fasten your seat belts because math is coming.
所以请保持注意集中 一大堆数学知识就要来了
On your left, you have a single perceptron with the input vector,
在左侧是单个感知器 带有输入向量
the weights and the bias and the sigmoid function inside the node.
权重 偏差和 sigmoid 函数 它们都在这个节点内
And on the right, we have a formula for the prediction,
右侧是预测所使用的公式
which is the sigmoid function of the linear function of the input.
输入先经过一个线性方程 再经过 sigmoid 函数
And below, we have a formula for the error,
下面是误差公式
which is the average of all points of
它是所有点的平均结果
the blue term for the blue points and the red term for the red points.
蓝色项和红色项分别代表蓝点和红点
And in order to descend from Mount Errorest,
为了从误差之巅上下来
we calculate the gradient.
我们需要计算梯度
And the gradient is simply the vector formed by all the partial derivatives of
梯度是误差函数关于权重（从 w1 到 wn）和偏差的偏导数
the error function with respect to the weights w1 up to wn and and the bias b.
所形成的向量
They correspond to these edges over here,
它们所对应的是这些边
and what do we do in a multilayer perceptron?
在多层感知器中该如何进行反向传播？
Well, this time it's a little more complicated but it's pretty much the same thing.
这种情况稍微复杂些 但本质上几乎一样
We have our prediction,
这是我们的预测结果
which is simply a composition of functions namely matrix multiplications and sigmoids.
其实就是一些复合函数 包括矩阵乘法和 sigmoid 函数
And the error function is pretty much the same,
误差函数几乎保持不变
except the ŷ is a bit more complicated.
只是 ŷ 稍微复杂些
And the gradient is pretty much the same thing,
梯度几乎一样
it's just much, much longer.
只是表达式长了很多
It's a huge vector where each entry is
它是一个庞大的向量
a partial derivative of the error with respect to each of the weights.
每一项分别是误差函数关于每个权重的偏导数
And these just correspond to all the edges.
这些项对应所有的边
If we want to write this more formally,
如果要写的更严谨一些
we recall that the prediction is a composition of sigmoids and matrix multiplications,
我们知道预测结果是 sigmoid 函数和矩阵乘法的复合
where these are the matrices and
这些是矩阵
the gradient is just going to be formed by all these partial derivatives.
梯度由所有这些偏导数组成
Here, it looks like a matrix but in reality,
这里看起来像个矩阵
it's just a long vector.
但实际上是个很长的向量
And the gradient descent is going to do the following;
梯度下降法将进行如下步骤
we take each weight,
我们拿出每个权重 wij(k)
w_i_j super k and we update it by adding a small number,
我们对其进行更新
the learning rate times the partial derivative of E with respect to that same weight.
加上一个小数字（也就是学习速率）乘以 E 相对于该权重的偏导数
This is the gradient descent step,
这是梯度下降的步骤
so it will give us new updated weight w_i_j super k prime.
这样将得到更新后的权重 wij’(k)
That step is going to give us a whole new model
于是就得到了一个全新的模型
with new weights that will classify the point much better.
它包含了新的权重 可以对点进行更准确的分类